<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Doggobot</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Doggobot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2019, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl Setup</title>
      <link>/blog/vinyl-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/vinyl-setup/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon,
Today, I thought it would be a great idea to share my audio equipment. I happen to love audio equipment quite a bit, and would say that music is a big part of my life. Now, Vinyl is one of the most unconventional way to listen to music, but the whole experience is a great treat, forcing you to listen to the music. I love the whole process and everything about it, and would love to share it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Pixi.js Development Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/pixi-js-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/pixi-js-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon,
For the past few months, I have been wanting to get into game development for quite some time. It was one of my passions as a kid, but I never thought I could do it until now. As stated earlier, I am a web developer, with a little over 1 year of developer experience. Every time I have tried, I got a little frustrated due to very high inconsistencies with an entire game engine framework vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Developer Equipment</title>
      <link>/blog/equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/equipment/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon,
I thought as an Initial post I would create a post talking about my development gear. From time to time, I always get people asking me why I choose to use my certain laptop, keyboard, etc. and I thought this would be a great time to give a rundown on why I use it, and why I have not upgraded in a long time.
As a tl;dr, here is a simple rundown:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal NAS / Plex / E-book server - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/server-build-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/server-build-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon,
Today, I wanted to talk about a future plan I have going on right now. Recently, I had found a Dell R640 for VERY cheap, but my main issue is where the server rack is located, I can not have it running at certain times, as it is very very loud. I am currently in the process of moving this specific server to a place where noise wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
